Office of Alumni Relations Records UA011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Alumni Relations Records
1850 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Alumni Relations
Joseph W. Morton
UA011
43.83 Linear Feet 38 boxes, 4 oversized folders
27 Audiovisual Object(s) 22 VHS and 5 U-matic videocassettes
15 Digital Object(s) 15 digital objects containing 368 files
11 Reels
5 Photographic Prints
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of Alumni Relations, 2005 -- 2020.
Arrangement
This collection is organized in fifteen series: Tufts Univesrity Office of Alumni Relations, event files; Tufts University Alumni Assocation and Jackson College Alumni Association; Oral Histories; Photographs and auido-visual materials; Photo Albums; Tufts Univesrity Office of Alumni Relations, Tufts Clubs; Tufts Univesrity Office of Alumni Relations, subject files; Tufts Univesrity Office of Alumni Relationsgive-aways; Secretary of Alumni Assocation, Fred Nickless; Secretary of Alumni Assocoation, Joseph W. Morton; 2017 accessions; 2018 accessions; 2019 accessions; Unprocessed Accessions; and 2020 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Alumni Relations (1924-present) was established in 1924 by the Tufts University Alumni Association and was administered by Tufts as the Office of the Alumni Secretary. The first Alumni Secretary was Joseph W. Morton A'11, who served from 1924-56. The Secretary handled alumni outreach, conducted fundraising for the Alumni Fund, created alumni directories, edited university publications, assisted with alumni career placement, and coordinated with the Alumni Council and the Tufts University Alumni Association. The Secretary was based in Cousens Gym and, after 1965, in Alumni House. The Office has been located at 80 George St. since 2007.
The office was greatly expanded by President Jean Mayer in 1978 as the Office of Alumni Relations under the direction of Richard A. Kelley A37 G38. The new Office played a crucial role in the "Campaign for Tufts," at the time the largest fundraising initiative in Tufts' history by far. In 1985, the Office's second director, Ronald Brinn A58, created Tuftonia's Day to encourage closer bonds between alumni and the university. The holiday is celebrated in mid-April every year to commemorate the signing of the Tufts charter and has become a global celebration of all things Tufts-related.
The office is administered by the University Advancement Division and overseen by the Senior Vice President for University Advancement as of 2018.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains scrapbooks, VHS tapes, U-matic tapes, audio reels and cassette tapes, slides, correspondence, office files, subject files, meeting minutes, event brochures, and memorabilia such as Frisbees and commemorative pens pertaining to alumni activities and relations. This collection also contains photographs of Tufts graduating classes and alumni events, student and alumni directories, and presentations.
University history; Student life; Alumni and Alumni Relations
- Tufts University Office of Alumni Relations, event files, 1959 -- 2000; 1995; UA011.001; 1.0 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains office files relating to the planning of alumni events including Tuftonia Day, Homecoming, and Alumni Parade.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by event type and chronologically within event.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day Scrolls, 1959 -- 1965; UA011.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1985; UA011.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1985; UA011.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1987; UA011.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1988; UA011.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1989; UA011.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Week, 1989; UA011.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Week, 1990; UA011.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Week, 1990; UA011.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1991; UA011.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1992; UA011.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Week, 1992; UA011.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day program, 1993; UA011.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1993; UA011.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1994; UA011.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1995; UA011.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Day, 1996; UA011.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Tuftonia's Week, 1997; UA011.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1979; UA011.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1982; UA011.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1985; UA011.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1986; UA011.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1986; UA011.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1987; UA011.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1989; UA011.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1990; UA011.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1991; UA011.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1993; UA011.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1994; UA011.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1995; UA011.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Homecoming, 1996; UA011.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend Parade, 1964; UA011.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, PEP booklet, 1973; UA011.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1984; UA011.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1985; UA011.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1986; UA011.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1987; UA011.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1988; UA011.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1989; UA011.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1990; UA011.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1991; UA011.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1992; UA011.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA011.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1994; UA011.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1995; UA011.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1996; UA011.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Career networking forums, 1997; UA011.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1996 -- 1998; UA011.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    Paris, 1996; London, 1998
  - Night at the Pops, 2000; UA011.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Program agenda reunion leaders' training session, 1988; UA011.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Reunions, 1986; UA011.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Annual events: Alumni Weekend, 1999; UA011.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
- Tufts University Alumni Association and Jackson College Alumni Association, 1910 -- 2014; 1929 -- 2001; UA011.002; 1.55 Linear Feet; 5 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains records on alumni groups, Tufts University Alumni Association and Jackson College Alumni Association, and memorabilia relating to these groups.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by alumni group.
  - Jackson Alumni: news clippings, 1929; UA011.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Alumni: association of Tufts alumni, UA011.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
    No Date Available
  - Jackson Alumni: Tufts Glasses, correspondence, UA011.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
    No date available.
  - Jackson Alumni: College Plates announcements/correspondence, 1947; UA011.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Alumni: Report of the Self Study Committee for Jackson College, 1967; UA011.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Alumni: correspondence, 1945 -- 1952; UA011.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Alumni: "Glossy cut of plate", 1948; UA011.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Alumni: Tufts plates, 1952; UA011.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Jackson Alumni: Tufts plates, 1931 -- 1941; UA011.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: New Hampshire Tufts Alliance, UA011.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: West Florida Tufts Alliance, 1996; UA011.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: Alumni weekend, 2001; UA011.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: Tufts Enlightenment series, 1989 -- 2001; UA011.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: Homecoming flyer, 2001; UA011.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: Travel Learn Program, 2000; UA011.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: amended by-laws, 1959; UA011.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: alumni innaugural reception, 1995; UA011.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: Sesquicentennial Memory Capsule time card, 2002; UA011.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: Atlanta Tufts Alliance, UA011.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - TUAA: "Ten Years of Good Stewardship", 1925; UA011.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - TUAA Class Ring brochure, 2010; UA011.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - TUAA Travel Learn Program, 2008; UA011.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - TUAA Travel Learn Program, 2011; UA011.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - TUAA Travel Learn Program, 2012; UA011.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - TUAA Travel Learn Program, 2014; UA011.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - TUAA Travel Learn Program, 2017; UA011.002.003.0026 (Box 3, Box 26)
  - High on the Hill, 1910 -- 1979; UA011.002.050.00001; Dixon, Linda J. (Box 50)
    Tufts University -- History
    - Allan D. Callow, 1979; UA011.002.050.00001.00001; Unknown (Box 50)
      Illustration from High on the Hill, 1979.
      People; Portraits; Callow, Allan D.
    - Students building bleachers, 1920; UA011.002.050.00001.00002; Unknown (Box 50)
      People; Students
    - Campus map, 1967; UA011.002.050.00001.00003; Unknown (Box 50)
    - View from Paige/Miner, 1910; UA011.002.050.00001.00004; Unknown (Box 50)
  - Traditions at Tufts, 1967; UA011.002.050.00002; Manning, Marjorie Gott (Box 50)
  - Printed materials, 2010; UA011.002.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Gift bag contents, 2010; UA011.002.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - A Light from the Hill 1860-2010 DVD, UA011.002.067.00003 (Box 67)
    DVD
  - Tote bag, 2010; UA011.002.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Pens, 2010; UA011.002.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Water glasses, 2010; UA011.002.067.00006 (Box 67)
    Two etched glasses.
- Oral histories, 1977; UA011.003; 10 Audiovisual Object(s); 2 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains oral histories with Dr. Nichols and Carpenter and Littleton.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Dr. Nichols, 1977-03-04; UA011.003.004.00001 (Box 4)
    Intercollegate football; Zeta-Psi history; professor Fay, German prof. and mountain climber; Pearson Lab (named after Frederick Stark Pearson); Frank Wren's house.
    Nichols, Robert L.
  - Dr. Nichols, 1977-03-04; UA011.003.005.00001 (Box 5)
    Portraits in Alumni Hall; Lewis Hall; John A Cousen; Edith Bush; Tufts men who fought in the Civil War; Frederick Hogdon; Tufts people in the Olympics; mayorality; freshman code; college song; freshman code(more); class spirit; prohibition; modern times.
  - Dr. Nichols, 1977-03-04; UA011.003.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Dorm and social life; stories; fraternities, honorary societies, sororities; class officers; first Boston radio at Tufts; Vietnam War; World War II; grounds and buildings men; comparing old and new faculty.
  - Dr. Nichols, 1977-04-25; UA011.003.007.00001 (Box 7)
    Fletcher class of 1876; college songs, life.
  - Dr Nichols, 1977-04-01; UA011.003.008.00001 (Box 8)
    Cousens Gym; Fred Hogdon; Alumni Day, June 1941; college music.
  - Dr Nichols, 1977-03-28; UA011.003.009.00001 (Box 9)
    Memorial steps; class of 1926; introduction; East and West Hall; Barnum, Wren, Miller, and Houston; prof. Fay; John Holmes; profs at Tufts. Date is approximate
  - Carpenter and Littleton #3, 1977-03-28; UA011.003.010.00001 (Box 10)
    Formal dinners with faculty; Glee Club; Christmas sing; fraternity parties; football games; train to Boston; girls not allowed to have cars, radios; radio tower; competition between freshman and sophmores; fraternity initiations. Date is approximate
  - Carpenter and Littleton #2, 1977-03-28; UA011.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
    Jumbo; radio at Tufts; prof. Dalbert; diapers on jumbo; horribles parade; mayorality; stories of Jumbo; dress codes; when Tufts was smaller; formal meals.
  - Carpenter and Nichols #1, 1977-03-28; UA011.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
    The Barnum Room, Jumbo; portrait of Barnum; museum donation; Jumbo's death; Jumbo came to Tufts; University of Bridgeport. Date is approximate
  - Carpenter add time, 1977; UA011.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
    Barnum museum, lounge. Date is approximate
- Photographs and audio-visual material, 1850 -- 2015; 1956 -- 1997; UA011.004; 3.95 Linear Feet; 27 Audiovisual Object(s)
  This series contains photographs and audio-visual material relating to various alumni events.
  This series is arranged by material type.
  - Alumni Weekend, 1964; UA011.004.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend parade, 1964; UA011.004.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1965; UA011.004.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1966; UA011.004.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Alumni portraits, 1930 -- 1954; UA011.004.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1967; UA011.004.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Alumni Council, 1951; UA011.004.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Misc. groups, 1955 -- 1965; UA011.004.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1962; UA011.004.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend parade, 1966; UA011.004.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Alumni Review, 1955; UA011.004.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Day, 1956; UA011.004.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1957; UA011.004.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1961; UA011.004.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Homecoming Day: group photos, 1959; UA011.004.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Summer Theatre, 1979; UA011.004.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Day, 1949; UA011.004.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Day, 1953; UA011.004.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Alumni, 1955; UA011.004.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Mrs. Emma Tufts Powers, UA011.004.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Musical groups with President Nils Yngve Wessell, UA011.004.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1947 officers, UA011.004.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Day, 1945; UA011.004.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1963; UA011.004.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Day, 1954; UA011.004.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Baseball team, 1915; UA011.004.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Negatives, 1931; UA011.004.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1948; UA011.004.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Leaders Symposium, 1967; UA011.004.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Brinn negatives, 1991; UA011.004.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Shore Club negatives, 1986; UA011.004.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Misc. photos, UA011.004.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - 26th Reunion, 1988; UA011.004.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1930 Reunion, UA011.004.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Beelzebubs at Tuftonias Day, 1986; UA011.004.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Nutrition Alumni Day, 1988; UA011.004.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Criterion, 1987; UA011.004.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Over 55 Dinner, UA011.004.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Class Day, 1993; UA011.004.014.00039 (Box 14)
  - Homecoming, 1988; UA011.004.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - Frederick Hauck, UA011.004.014.00041 (Box 14)
  - Lousie Nevelson, 1985; UA011.004.014.00042 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Criterion: Class of 1937, 1987; UA011.004.014.00043 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1983 10 year Reunion, 1993; UA011.004.014.00044 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1943 50 year Reunion, 1993; UA011.004.014.00045 (Box 14)
  - Class of 1968 25 year Reunion, 1993; UA011.004.014.00046 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA011.004.014.00047 (Box 14)
  - Regional alliances greetings to President DiBiaggio on Inauguration, UA011.004.014.00048 (Box 14)
  - Misc. photos, UA011.004.014.00049 (Box 14)
  - Alumni photos, UA011.004.014.00050 (Box 14)
  - Photo album: Part I, 1920; UA011.004.014.00051 (Box 14)
  - Photo album: Part II, 1920; UA011.004.014.00052 (Box 14)
  - Photo album: Tufts students & faculty, 1920; UA011.004.014.00053 (Box 14)
  - Photo album: Tufts students & faculty, 1955; UA011.004.014.00054 (Box 14)
  - Photo album: Tufts students & faculty, 1955; UA011.004.014.00055 (Box 14)
  - Photo album: Tufts students & faculty, 1955; UA011.004.014.00056 (Box 14)
  - Great Tuftonian Train Ride II, 1993; UA011.004.014.00057 (Box 14)
  - Misc. photos, 1994; UA011.004.014.00058 (Box 14)
  - Misc. photos, 1990; UA011.004.014.00059 (Box 14)
  - Misc. photos, UA011.004.014.00060 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1992; UA011.004.014.00061 (Box 14)
  - Misc, photos, UA011.004.014.00062 (Box 14)
  - Alumni camps, 1987; UA011.004.014.00063 (Box 14)
  - Campus photos, 1990; UA011.004.014.00064 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1991; UA011.004.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Misc. photographs, UA011.004.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1987; UA011.004.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1992; UA011.004.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Class of 1931, UA011.004.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Field Representatives Group, 1963 -- 1966; UA011.004.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Boston Tufts Club, 1960; UA011.004.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Training conference for field representatives, 1966; UA011.004.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Brooks Johnson (Stanford Track Director/Women's Olympic Track Coach), 1984; UA011.004.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Homecoming flag, 1985; UA011.004.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Robert Toyofuku on Ala Moana Beach, Hawaii, UA011.004.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Tuftonias Day, 1989; UA011.004.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - New York Tufts Alliance, UA011.004.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Zeta Psi House, 1900; UA011.004.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Alumni, UA011.004.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Alumni Relations Team, 1984; UA011.004.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Alumni House, UA011.004.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Campus, 1960; UA011.004.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Distinguished service awards, 1945; UA011.004.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Jackson Daughters, 1963; UA011.004.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - New York Tufts Club, 1966; UA011.004.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - North Shore Tufts Club, 1954; UA011.004.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1986; UA011.004.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Day, 1988; UA011.004.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Tuftonia, winter, 1994; UA011.004.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA011.004.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1991; UA011.004.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1988; UA011.004.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1960; UA011.004.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1950; UA011.004.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Day, 1952; UA011.004.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Alumni Day, 1951; UA011.004.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - San Diego & California Tufts Clubs, 1950; UA011.004.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut & New Hampshire Tufts Clubs, 1962; UA011.004.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Philadelphia Tufts Club, 1960; UA011.004.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Vermont Tufts Club, 1965; UA011.004.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Mohawk-Hudson, 1957; UA011.004.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Misc. photos, UA011.004.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Class of 1950 65th Reunion photograph, 2015-05-15; UA011.004.016.00017 (Box 16)
    photographic print
  - Misc. slides, UA011.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Misc. slides, UA011.004.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - January, 1989; UA011.004.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Misc. slides, UA011.004.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Misc. slides, UA011.004.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Ronald C. Brinn, Talloires, 1984; UA011.004.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Ronald C. Brinn, European trip, 1984; UA011.004.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Campus, 1960; UA011.004.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Bucky Spurr, 1994; UA011.004.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Tufts students, UA011.004.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Students and campus, UA011.004.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Students, faculty and campus, UA011.004.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Students, faculty and campus, UA011.004.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Misc. slides, UA011.004.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Misc. slides, UA011.004.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Video: "That memorable year, 1963", UA011.004.019.00001 (Box 19)
    videocassette
  - Video: "A San Franciscans Tuftonia's Day", 1993; UA011.004.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Video: "Choate Rosemary Hall", UA011.004.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Video: "Tufts Alumni", UA011.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Video: "Multi-media portfolio tape", UA011.004.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Video: "Tufts University", UA011.004.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Video: "Music at Carnegie Mellon University", UA011.004.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Video: "Touchdown for Tufts", featuring Rick Hauck and Rob Brin., UA011.004.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Video: "Waterform", UA011.004.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - Video: "The Great Tuftonia Trainride promo-tape", UA011.004.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - Video: Tufts Alumni Weekend Comeback Campaign, "The Making of the Precedent, 1988", UA011.004.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - Video: "Tufts University 97' spot for Sony", 1997; UA011.004.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - Video: "The Great Tuftonian Trainride II", UA011.004.031.00001 (Box 31)
  - Video: "Tufts Candlelight Ceremony", 1991-05-11; UA011.004.032.00001 (Box data_value_missing_da4ec31c85c1a90d30417ea64ae0ee40)
  - Video: "Tufts Candlelight Ceremony", 1993; UA011.004.033.00001 (Box data_value_missing_da4ec31c85c1a90d30417ea64ae0ee40)
  - Video: "Tufts Candlelight Ceremonies", 1988 -- 1990; UA011.004.034.00001 (Box data_value_missing_da4ec31c85c1a90d30417ea64ae0ee40)
  - Video: "Tuftonia's Day, Times Square", 1991; UA011.004.035.00001 (Box 35)
  - Video: "Tufts vs Amherst, Homecoming", 1993; UA011.004.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Video: "Tufts University slide show transfer", UA011.004.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Video: "Nick Paleologos, Lieutenant Governor", UA011.004.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Video: "Tufts Beelzebubs", UA011.004.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Video: "Inaguration Weekend Ceremonies for Tufts University President John DiBiaggio", 1993; UA011.004.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Video: "Tufts University Tuftonia's Day 30 second spot", UA011.004.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - Video: "Tufts Beelzebubs", UA011.004.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Video: "The Great Tuftonian Trainride", Tuftonia's Week, the Beelzebubs., 1989; UA011.004.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Video: "Touchdown at Tufts, and Astronaut's Homecoming", UA011.004.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Video: "Channel 5 News Report of Shuttle-Rick Hauck, UA011.004.045.00001 (Box 45)
  - Video: "The Great Tuftonian Trainride II", UA011.004.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - Video: "Profile: Rick Hauck, space footage, shuttle landing", UA011.004.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - Audio Cassette: Tuftonia's Day Ceremony, 1986; UA011.004.048.00001 (Reel 48)
    audio tape
  - Audio Cassette: Tuftonia's Day Kickoff, 1987; UA011.004.048.00002 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Tuftonia's Day Proclamation Ceremony, UA011.004.048.00003 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Tufts University Jackson Jills, "Sidetracked", 1989 -- 1990; UA011.004.048.00004 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: The Jills Demo Tape, UA011.004.048.00005 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: The Amalgamates, "The Chartreuse album", 1989; UA011.004.048.00006 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: The Amalgamates, "Quater Past Six", 1991; UA011.004.048.00007 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Cayuga's Waiters, "Maintaining the Illusion", 1989; UA011.004.048.00008 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: The Tufts University Beelzebubs, UA011.004.048.00009 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Mark Russell Comedy Special, 1987; UA011.004.048.00010 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Mark Russell Comedy Special, 1987; UA011.004.048.00011 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Mark Russell Comedy Special, 1988; UA011.004.048.00012 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Tracy Chapman, 1988; UA011.004.048.00013 (Reel 48)
  - Audio Cassette: Hot Ginger, UA011.004.048.00014 (Reel 48)